All I it's time to get our hands dirty.
With AWS the first thing you're gonna do is
create an AWS account.
If you need to work with AWS, you need an account.
So what's an account? An account is just
like your credit card account, right?
You kind of buy something and you pay to the bank later.
Similarly, on AWS you're gonna be creating a lot of stuffs.
So AWS needs to bill you for what to create.
So you'll get an account now
and in the real world when you join a company,
accounts are already created only for us to practice.
We are getting an account. Now,
the next few videos will actually let you do that.
It'll demonstrate to you how
to create an account and you can do that.
The next step is to create an admin user.
Now, what's an admin user? This is required for us
to practice on AWS account.
Okay? Now, again, in the real world,
you'll be told how to log in.
You will not log in with an admin user.
The third step is to download an install
A-W-S-C-L-I Command line interface.
So what's A-W-S-C-L-I?
It's a software that lets you access AWS
resources using commands.
Again, when you join a company,
you are given a laptop, right?
So the first thing you'll do is
get A-W-S-C-L-I installed on your laptop,
and the next step, you'll actually do a, an activity
that will use A-W-S-C-L-I command, okay?
Which is to configure A-W-S-C-L-I on your system,
even in the real world in your companies.
You will configure A-W-S-C-L-I on your laptop,
and there's a one time activity that you do on your laptop.
The next few videos will demonstrate how to actually do all
of this, to get that going.